{
    "subject": "resource/Steve_Zahn",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Steve Zahn",
    "human_readable": "The label of Steve Zahn is Steve Zahn.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9444071650505066,
            "question": "Does the label 'Steve Zahn' refer to a person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9105490446090698,
            "question": "Is Steve Zahn a person?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9013559818267822,
            "question": "Who is Steve Zahn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8466122150421143,
            "question": "What is the name of Steve Zahn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8238616585731506,
            "question": "What is Steve Zahn known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7708860039710999,
            "question": "Is there any other information available about Steve Zahn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7551734447479248,
            "question": "What are some of Steve Zahn's notable works?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.697706401348114,
            "question": "Where can I find more information about Steve Zahn?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6764417290687561,
            "question": "Is there anything else associated with the name 'Steve Zahn'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6414607763290405,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Steve Zahn?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Steve Zahn is Steve Zahn.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4371_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else associated with the name 'Steve Zahn'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4371_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I find more information about Steve Zahn?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4371_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of Steve Zahn's notable works?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4371_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4371_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4371_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4371_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4371_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4371_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4371_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4371_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4371_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4371_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4371_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Steve Zahn family wife Robyn Peterman\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents confirm that Steve Zahn's wife is indeed named Robyn Peterman. Additionally, it is mentioned that they have two children together."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context correctly identifies \"Steve Zahn\" as the subject being discussed, and there are no contradictions or discrepancies that would invalidate this simple identity statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}